Register of the Henry S. Rowen papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- 2016 Incremental Materials, 1958-2015
  - Photographs, 1963-2006
    - Oversize photographs, 1966, 2002, undated (Box-folder 87: 4)
    - Miscellany, 2002, undated (Box-folder 85: 20)
      Unidentified photographs of Rowen.
  - Videorecordings, 2005-2015 (Box 86)
    DVDs.
    - The John Raisian Interview, 2015
    - Ralph Landau: A Celebration, 2005
    - Tough Times Ahead: Foreign Policy Changes for the New President, 2009 January 8
    - A Conversation with George P. Shultz and Henry Rowen, 2006
    - Diminishing Natural Resources: Recognizing Limitations, Responding to the Challenges, 2009 October 20-21
    - Ideas in Action: 60 Years of RAND, 2005
    - "Innovation in Energy Efficiency," SPRIE workshop, 2009 February
      Two discs.
    - Innovation Beyond Boundaries: New Partnerships for Advancing Smart and Green Living, 2011 June 30
    - Proceedings of Academy of Innovation and Entrepreneurship, 2010
  - Memorabilia, undated (Boxes 88-89)
    Medals, awards, and plaques awarded to Rowen.
- Not yet described (Boxes 90-93)